Register to the Joseph Abraham Mendenhall papers, 1927-2011
Hoover Institution Archives
- Subject File, 1954-2009 (Box 18)
  - Vietnam and Laos
    - General, 1980-2008 (Folder 18: 5)
      Printed articles.
    - Texas Tech University Vietnam Center, 2003-2006 (Folder 18: 6)
      Correspondence, conference agenda and printed matter. Includes conference papers from 2003 Conference on the Rise and Fall of Ngo Dinh Diem.
  - Miscellany, 1954-2009 (Folder 18: 7)
    Notes, printed articles, and other printed matter, mainly re American domestic and foreign policy.
- Photographs, 1949 (Folder 18: 8)
  Three group photographs of Joseph Mendenhall and other Foreign Service officers.
- Declassified U.S. Government Records (Box 18)
  Formerly security-classified records of the U.S. government, released in full or in part. Arranged chronologically by date of release by Hoover.
  - 2015 November release of records, 1947-1948, 1951,1968 (Box-folder 18: 9)
    Career-related records, including a family budget while Mendenhall was Vice Consul in Turkey, a letter of recommendation, memoranda written by Mendenhall regarding his career, a report, and a letter from William H. Sullivan regarding a job opportunity.